happened
Om Om
[Music]
Hello friends, a very warm welcome to
all of you on my YouTube channel. I am your
help content Kajal. Today in this video, I have
brought for you a gas plant. If
you are visiting my channel for the first time,
please subscribe to my channel.
Please like my video and click the bell icon
so that you keep getting the latest updates. Regarding this,
let's
start the video.
Please help me. Shopping
is set up
this afternoon. Stage C is something that can
wipe out all your savings in one go. The
best way to avoid such a problem is to
buy a good health insurance policy that can
come in handy in urgent times. We have prepared a very tasty product for you.
After that, we are suggesting you
this product called
Arey Yaar. It is a comprehensive health insurance
product. It covers your smallest
illness like viral infection, skin
infection, fever, to major
illness like cancer, hand dhat hai aakhri and
transplant. If someone dies due to all these things, then it
bears the expenses of his hospitalization.  And this same
hassle of going to the hospital and
leaving the hospital has been
reduced for people like you. This
plan means that if someone goes to a doctor, the
doctor will also cover the cost of the
tests they ask you to undergo,
and the cost of the medicines. All these things will be
covered under the Priyanka Hospitalization Valid. Apart from this, the Cheer
product has many attractive features for you,
such as the dormant feature. If
you have purchased a policy for ₹10 and
due to a large consignment, your entire
property goes to Bigg Boss, then there is no cover left
for your family for the remaining time of the year. Keeping
this in mind,
we have introduced this benefit called
automatic recharge. Yes,
at such times, it recharges an additional ₹1000000
to your policy, which
you can use for someone else's benefit
or add it for another Swami Mangal.
Not only this, if you want, you
can also avail unlimited automatic recharge benefits with the help of this.  The recharge
facility can be used unlimited times.
One great thing about the Clear plan is
that there's no surcharge, meaning
even a 100-year-old can buy a Care plan.
Once purchased, they can
renew it for life. It's
possible that
you'll ask, "Ma'am, if
I'm not hospitalized, will they take
out my printout?" Look, it's
not like that at all. The opposite is true.
In which college can you get a health checkup every year? You can get it done the very
next day after receiving the plan,
not just mention it.
Apart from this, there's a great feature called the "
Dhokale Bonus," with the help of which
your term insurance policy increases every year.
With the help of Anti-Super, your
non-HIM donor can go up to 1000 percent of the term insurance.
Besides these excellent benefits, the
Care plan offers many other
options. For example, if you
want OPD coverage,
you have a benefit option called Pretty
Clear, which ranges from 50 to 60 percent.  It also covers
OPD expenses up to Rs.1000, consultations,
prescribed diagnostics and family.
Apart from this, if you do
not find the premium affordable, then you can avail this at a discount of
15% by just choosing an option.
Apart from this, you get Delhi Alarms benefits,
which on your decision
gives you a benefit of Rs.1000 to Rs.1000, which you can use
for other expenses other than Heart Foundation,
such as travel,
food and drinks. Apart from this, there
is a very good coverage of International Second
PM, with the help of which, if you want, you can use the services of a
hospital and medical expert Chetna
and
can check whether the health is working properly or
not.
This is a specialist health
insurance company, that is, it is THC and with
your help, in a very short time, it has
made a place in the market, like
in the last year's calendar 2018 and 19, there is about 20 lakh
fame, our company has grown by more than 765 percent.
So this was a little information about the Care Hath
Zonal Plan,
for more information you
can contact us with the help of the WhatsApp number shown on the screen
and if you have come to my channel for the first time and
you liked this video then please do
not forget to subscribe to my channel
so that you keep getting the latest updates, thank
you for watching.